Naveed Ahmed Contact

Web Developer

I'm a professional website developer with over 8 years experience. Expert in developing websites with Wordpress, PHP, JS, HTML, SQL and C#.

Broad experience on Linux and Windows platforms, and solid knowledge of applications development and practices, I will be a valuable addition to any team.





12 Packard Cl. Ingleburn, Sydney 2565



+61 468 828 940



inaveedahmed@gmail.com



Experience

2015 - 2016

Red Rooster

Front-End Developer - Contract

Develop responsive mobile ordering web application using Angular.JS, HTML5, SCSS, Gulp, Git. Handling web request via MobileDen's REST API.

2014 - 2015

Symits Solutions

Senior Web Developer

Responsibilities including but not limited to web development, code optimization and contribute towards product design specification improvement. Managing workflow with agile development methodology.

Work mostly with modular web based applications, servicing API's and controllers involving android and ios.

2009 - 2014

Axproz

Associate Manager (Web Development)

Coordinate the resources and processes to deliver technology-enabled products and services. Architects solutions by studying existing technology architecture and evaluating solution alternatives with a specific emphasis on usability, performance and scalability.

Develop/optimize web services, custom CRM/OMS, and web application based on multiple frameworks.

2007 - 2009

Freelancing

Web Developer

Work on various freelance projects on different framework like Angular.JS, Bootstrap, Cordova, WordPress.



Education

2007

ZAS College of Arts

Diploma, Multimedia Operational Manager

Covers the skills and techniques needed to create professional-looking graphics, visual effects, motion graphics and animations.

2005

Beacon Askari College

Intermediate, Pre-Engineering





Web Application



UX / UI Design



Graphic Design



SEO Strategy





Photoshop / Illustrator



REST / SOAP / WCF / WSE



PHP / OOP MySQL



.Net / C# / MSSQL



Bootstrap / SCSS CSS3 / HTML5



Angular / Node WP / CodeIgnitor



¡Query / ¡S



Cpanel / AWS /



linkedin.com/in/inaveedahmed



twitter.com/i_naveedahmed



inaveed.com



Naveed Ahmed

Web Designer / Developer

Development Projects



RedRooster - Australia

Angular, HTML5, SCSS

Responsive design, angular web application integrated with REST API providing online ordering system.

Yumyummi

PHP, Android(java), REST, CI

A web, android and iOS application on agile development method that provide food guide for school kids in USA.

CentralHMS

PHP, MySQL, REST

A hotel management system build on custom php framework. Handling online booking,

Lancerhop

C#, MSSQL, WCF

Online writer management system consist of Billing, Work Assingment, Plagrism Testing, Accounts, Work Delivery, User Activity Modules.

Web Traffic Tester

C#, Selenium

Web traffic generator application using selenium and MSSQL. Link, SERP and Player modules.

AMS

C#, MSSQL, Moznet, WSE

Employee monotoring system with auto timesheet with payroll, leave, food, timecard, late and bulletin modules.

Urban Living (wordpress)

http://92101urbanliving.com/

- Design
- 3rd Party API

iQuery/Ajax

- **Custom WP**
- PHP, MySQL
- Google API
- **RETS DB**

Homecare Assistance

http://homecareassistance.com/

- Design
- CloudFlare
- Custom WP
- PHP, MySQL
- HTML, CSS3
- Ajax/ jQuery

Digital Menu Board

http://bit.ly/Yumyummi-menu-board

- Design
- PHP, MySQL
- HTML5 / CSS3
- Ajax/jQuery
- **REST Api**
- WebDB

Contentproz

http://contentproz.net/

- Wireframing
- C#, MSSQL
- Design
- Ajax
- HTML, CSS
- WebAPI
- iQuery

SABA SEO

http://sabaseo.com/

- Design
- PHP, MySQL
- Wordpress
- Ajax
- HTML5, CSS3
- jQuery